Hello I'm Sifu Mallon with the Clearwater Kung Fu Center.
This is Kung Fu for health.
This how to is on Jump Kick, this is called Heel Kick Double Jump Heel Kick.
Okay, so the Heel Kick, just demonstrating it for you, is a hinging kick.
This is where your knee lifts and pushes out.
Okay, now we're using this kick on three different actions.
The first kick is just kind of like a set up for your timing.
So to start it, right, you just keep your hands on by your side, you step, heel kick.
Step down, now your left knee is going to lift, then instead of just tucking your leg like this, okay, for a normal jump, you're going to throw your left foot out and heel kick.
As soon as you feel your left foot at the height of its action, you're going to jump and heel kick with your right foot, land.
Again, when your jump kicking, you're goal is to get your kicks head or above, that's the reason you're jumping to kick higher.
Okay, going into the combination for you quick.
I step one, double.
Again, I step one, double.
Different angle for you.
I step one, heel kick, step down, double jump heel kick.
This is Heel Kick Double Jump Heel Kick.